**********************************************************************
*
*  Production Version Release
* 
*  Microsoft Windows* 10 64 bit 
*
*  Intel(R) Serial IO Driver 
*
*  June 2015
*
*  NOTE:  This document refers to systems containing the 
*         following Intel processors/chipsets: 
*
*     Intel® Pentium® processor or Intel® Celeron® processor N- & J- series
*
*	
*  Installation Information
*
*  This document makes references to products developed by
*  Intel. There are some restrictions on how these products
*  may be used, and what information may be disclosed to
*  others. Please read the Disclaimer section and contact
*  your Intel field representative if you would like more
*  information.
*
**********************************************************************
**********************************************************************
*  DISCLAIMER: Intel is making no claims of usability,
*  efficacy or warranty.  The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE
*  AGREEMENT contained herein completely defines the license
*  and use of this software.
*
*  This document contains information on products in the 
*  design phase of development. The information here is 
*  subject to change without notice. Do not finalize a 
*  design with this information.
**********************************************************************
**********************************************************************

**********************************************************************
*  CONTENTS OF THIS DOCUMENT
**********************************************************************

This document contains the following sections:

1.  System Requirements
2.  Installing the Software
3.  Verifying Installation of the Software
4.  Identifying the Software Version Number

**********************************************************************
*  1.  SYSTEM REQUIREMENTS
**********************************************************************

1. The system must contain one of the following Intel
   Chipsets/Processors:

   Intel® Pentium® processor or Intel® Celeron® processor N- & J- series

2. The software should be installed on systems with at
   least 1 GB of system memory.

3. There should be sufficient hard disk space in the
   directory on the system in order to install this
   software.

   The drivers included with this distribution package are 
   designed to function with Windows* 10 64-bit OS available at the 
   time of release of this package.

Please check with your system provider to determine the
operating system and Intel Chipset used in your system.


**********************************************************************
*  2.  INSTALLING THE SOFTWARE
**********************************************************************
The kit package contains two sub-packages: 
a) Installer executable:
Double-click on the executable file to install the driver.

b) Folder with CAT, INF, SYS files for manual installation:
Locate the INF files. 
Right click on the INF file and select 
"Install" option from the menu to start the installation.


**********************************************************************
*  3.  VERIFYING INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE
**********************************************************************
1. Launch the "Device Manager" by holding down Windows 
    Key + X on the keyboard to open the tools Menus and select 
    the "Device Manager" from the menu.

2. Verify the following devices should be listed and not 
   yellow banged. If not, the driver is not 
   installed correctly. 

	I2C Host Controller 
	GPIO Host Controller 

Drivers will not be installed for controllers that are not 
enabled by the BIOS. The list of controllers is platform/BIOS 
configuration dependent.

**********************************************************************
*  4. IDENTIFYING THE SOFTWARE VERSION NUMBER
**********************************************************************
1. Launch the "Device Manager" by holding down Windows 
    Key + X on the keyboard to open the tools Menus and select 
    the "Device Manager" from the menu.

2. Select any of the following devices:

	I2C Host Controller 
	GPIO Host Controller 
	
3. Click on the "Driver" tab and note the driver version.

**********************************************************************
* INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT 
* (OEM / IHV / ISV Distribution & Single User)
**********************************************************************

IMPORTANT - READ BEFORE COPYING, INSTALLING OR 
USING. 
Do not use or load this software and any associated materials 
(collectively, the “Software”) until you have carefully read the 
following terms and conditions. By loading or using the Software, 
you agree to the terms of this Agreement. If you do not wish to so 
agree, do not install or use the Software.

Please Also Note:
   If you are an Original Equipment Manufacturer (OEM), 
   Independent    Hardware Vendor (IHV), or Independent 
   Software Vendor (ISV), this complete LICENSE AGREEMENT 
   applies; If you are an End-User, then only Exhibit A, the INTEL 
   SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT, applies.

For OEMs, IHVs, and ISVs:

LICENSE. This Software is licensed for use only in conjunction 
with Intel component products.  Use of the Software in 
conjunction with non-Intel component products is not licensed 
hereunder. Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Intel grants to 
You a nonexclusive, nontransferable, worldwide, fully paid-up 
license under Intel’s copyrights to:
   a) use, modify and copy Software internally for Your own 
       development and maintenance purposes; and
   b) modify, copy and distribute Software, including derivative 
       works of the Software, to Your end-users, but only under a 
       license agreement with terms at least as restrictive as those 
       contained in Intel's Final, Single User License Agreement, 
       attached as Exhibit A; and
   c) modify, copy and distribute the end-user documentation 
       which may accompany the Software, but only in association 
       with the Software.

If You are not the final manufacturer or vendor of a computer 
system or software program incorporating the Software, then 
You may transfer a copy of the Software, including derivative 
works of the Software (and related end-user documentation) to 
Your recipient for use in accordance with the terms of this 
Agreement, provided such recipient agrees to be fully bound by 
the terms hereof.  
You shall not otherwise assign, sublicense, lease, or in any other 
way transfer or disclose Software to any third party. You shall not 
reverse- compile, disassemble or otherwise reverse-engineer 
the Software.

Except as expressly stated in this Agreement, no license or right 
is granted to You directly or by implication, inducement, estoppel 
or otherwise. Intel shall have the right to inspect or have an 
independent auditor inspect Your relevant records to verify Your 
compliance with the terms and conditions of this Agreement.

CONFIDENTIALITY.   If You wish to have a third party 
consultant or subcontractor ("Contractor") perform work on Your 
behalf which involves access to or use of Software, You shall 
obtain a written confidentiality agreement from the Contractor 
which contains terms and obligations with respect to access 
to or use of Software no less restrictive than those set forth in 
this Agreement and excluding any distribution rights, and use for 
any other purpose. Otherwise, You shall not disclose the terms 
or existence of this Agreement or use Intel's name in any 
publications, advertisements, or other announcements without 
Intel's prior written consent.  You do not have any rights to use 
any Intel trademarks or logos.

OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE AND COPYRIGHTS. Title to all 
copies of the Software remains with Intel or its suppliers. The 
Software is copyrighted and protected by the laws of the United 
States and other countries, and international treaty provisions. 
You may not remove any copyright notices from the Software. 
Intel may make changes to the Software, or to items referenced 
therein, at any time and without notice, but is not obligated to 
support or update the Software. 
Except as otherwise expressly provided, Intel grants no express 
or implied right under Intel patents, copyrights, trademarks, or 
other intellectual property rights. You may transfer the Software 
only if the recipient agrees to be fully bound by these terms and 
if you retain no copies of the Software.

LIMITED MEDIA WARRANTY.  If the Software has been delivered 
by Intel on physical media, Intel warrants the media to be free 
from material physical defects for a period of ninety (90) days 
after delivery by Intel. If such a defect is found, return the media 
to Intel for replacement or alternate delivery of the Software 
as Intel may select.

EXCLUSION OF OTHER WARRANTIES. EXCEPT AS 
PROVIDED ABOVE, THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" 
WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY 
KIND, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, 
NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR 
PURPOSE.  Intel does not warrant or assume responsibility for 
the accuracy or completeness of any information, text, graphics, 
links or other items contained within the Software.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEL OR ITS 
SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER 
(INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, 
BUSINESS INTERRUPTION OR LOST INFORMATION) ARISING 
OUT OF THE USE OF OR IN-ABILITY TO USE THE 
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF INTEL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE 
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS 
PROHIBIT EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR 
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL 
DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO 
YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER LEGAL RIGHTS THAT 
VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION. 

TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT. Intel may terminate this 
Agreement at any time if you violate its terms. Upon termination, 
you will immediately destroy the Software or return all copies of 
the Software to Intel.
 
APPLICABLE LAWS. Claims arising under this Agreement shall 
be governed by the laws of California, excluding its principles of 
conflict of laws and the United Nations Convention on Contracts 
for the Sale of Goods. You may not export the Software in 
violation of applicable export laws and regulations. 
Intel is not obligated under any other agreements unless they are 
in writing and signed by an authorized representative of Intel.

GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. The Software is 
provided with "RESTRICTED RIGHTS." Use, duplication, or 
disclosure by the Government is subject to restrictions as set 
forth in FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or their 
successors. Use of the Software by the Government constitutes 
acknowledgment of Intel's proprietary rights therein. Contractor 
or Manufacturer is Intel Corporation, 
2200 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, CA 95052.


EXHIBIT “A” 
INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT (Final, Single User)

IMPORTANT - READ BEFORE COPYING, INSTALLING OR 
USING. 
Do not use or load this software and any associated materials 
(collectively, the “Software”) until you have carefully read the 
following terms and conditions. By loading or using the Software, 
you agree to the terms of this Agreement. If you do not wish to 
so agree, do not install or use the Software.

LICENSE. You may copy the Software onto a single computer for 
your personal, noncommercial use, and you may make one 
back-up copy of the Software, subject to these conditions: 
1.This Software is licensed for use only in conjunction with Intel 
   component products.  Use of the Software in conjunction with 
   non-Intel component products is not licensed hereunder. 
2.You may not copy, modify, rent, sell, distribute or transfer any 
   part of the Software except as provided in this Agreement, and 
   you agree to prevent unauthorized copying of the Software.
3.You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the 
   Software. 
4. You may not sublicense or permit simultaneous use of the 
    Software by more than one user.
5.The Software may contain the software or other property of 
    third party suppliers, some of which may be identified in, and 
    licensed in accordance with, any enclosed “license.txt” file 
    or other text or file. 

OWNERSHIP OF SOFTWARE AND COPYRIGHTS. Title to all 
copies of the Software remains with Intel or its suppliers. The 
Software is copyrighted and protected by the laws of the United 
States and other countries, and international treaty provisions. 
You may not remove any copyright notices from the Software. 
Intel may make changes to the Software, or to items referenced 
therein, at any time without notice, but is not obligated to support 
or update the Software. Except as otherwise expressly provided, 
Intel grants no express or implied right under Intel patents, 
copyrights, trademarks, or other intellectual property rights. 
You may transfer the Software only if the recipient agrees to be 
fully bound by these terms and if you retain no copies of the 
Software.

LIMITED MEDIA WARRANTY.  If the Software has been delivered 
by Intel on physical media, Intel warrants the media to be free 
from material physical defects for a period of ninety (90) days 
after delivery by Intel. If such a defect is found, return the media 
to Intel for replacement or alternate delivery of the Software 
as Intel may select.

EXCLUSION OF OTHER WARRANTIES. EXCEPT AS 
PROVIDED ABOVE, THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" 
WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY 
KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, 
NONINFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR 
PURPOSE.  
Intel does not warrant or assume responsibility for the accuracy 
or completeness of any information, text, graphics, links or other 
items contained within the Software.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEL OR ITS 
SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER 
(INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS, 
BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOST INFORMATION) 
ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR IN-ABILITY TO USE THE 
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF INTEL HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE 
POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS 
PROHIBIT EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR 
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONSEQUENTIAL OR 
INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY 
NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU MAY ALSO HAVE OTHER LEGAL 
RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO 
JURISDICTION. 

TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT. Intel may terminate this 
Agreement at any time if you violate its terms. Upon termination, 
you will immediately destroy the Software or return all copies of 
the Software to Intel.
 
APPLICABLE LAWS. Claims arising under this Agreement shall 
be governed by the laws of California, excluding its principles of 
conflict of laws and the United Nations Convention on Contracts 
for the Sale of Goods. You may not export the Software in 
violation of applicable export laws and regulations. 
Intel is not obligated under any other agreements unless they are 
in writing and signed by an authorized representative of Intel.

GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS. The Software is 
provided with "RESTRICTED RIGHTS." Use, duplication, or 
disclosure by the Government is subject to restrictions as set 
forth in FAR52.227-14 and DFAR252.227-7013 et seq. or their 
successors. Use of the Software by the Government constitutes 
acknowledgment of Intel's proprietary rights therein. Contractor 
or Manufacturer is Intel Corporation, 
2200 Mission College Blvd., Santa Clara, CA 95052.

 
SLA/OEM/IHV/RBK/ April 23, 2004
**********************************************************************
* DISCLAIMER
**********************************************************************
Intel is making no claims of usability, efficacy or 
warranty.The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT 
contained herein completely defines the license and use of this 
software.
**********************************************************************
Information in this document is provided in connection with Intel 
products. Except as expressly stated in the INTEL SOFTWARE 
LICENSE AGREEMENT contained herein, no license,express or 
implied, by estoppel or otherwise, to any intellectual property 
rights is granted by this document.
Except as provided in Intel's Terms and Conditions of Sale for 
such products, Intel assumes no liability whatsoever, and Intel 
disclaims any express or implied warranty, relating to sale and/or 
use of Intel products, including liability or warranties relating to 
fitness for a particular purpose, merchantability or infringement 
of any patent, copyright or other intellectual property right. 
Intel products are not intended for use in medical, lifesaving, or 
life-sustaining applications.

**********************************************************************
* Intel Corporation disclaims all warranties and 
* liabilities for the use of this document, the software 
* and the information contained herein, and assumes no
* responsibility for any errors which may appear in this
* document or the software, nor does Intel make a 
* commitment to update the information or software 
* contained herein. Intel reserves the right to make 
* changes to this document or software at any time, without
* notice.
**********************************************************************

* Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of 
others.

Copyright (c) 2015 Intel Corporation.  All rights reserved.
